learnersedgeinc.com 2013-10-30

# 

## Privacy Policy

Learner’s Edge has created this Privacy Policy to explain why we collect particular information and how we will protect your personal privacy within our Web site and within our organization. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Web site located at the URL [www.LearnersEdgeInc.com](http://www.learnersedgeinc.com/) and within Learner’s Edge Inc.

In order to fully understand your rights we encourage you to read this Privacy Policy. Learner’s Edge reserves the right at any time and without notice to change this Privacy Policy simply by posting such changes on our Site. Any such change will be effective immediately upon posting.

Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to your privacy, this Privacy Policy notifies you of;   
1\. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected;   
2\. Who collects such information;   
3\. How such information is used;   
4\. With whom your information may be shared;   
5\. What choices you have regarding collection, use and distribution of your information;   
6\. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control;   
7\. And, how you can correct any inaccuracies in your information.

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Learner’s Edge by sending an email to [info@LearnersEdgeInc.com](mailto:info@LearnersEdgeInc.com). Please reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.

**What Information We Collect and How We Use That Information:**   
Our online registration forms require users to give us contact information that may include name, email address, address, specialty areas, and similar information. We do not store credit card numbers from our visitors on our web site.

**Disclosure and Visitor Choice:**  
We do not share your name and address information nor email addresses with other organizations, unless necessary, for academic reasons, with your selected academic partner.

**Access To The Personal Data We May Hold About You:**  
You can ask us for the specific data that we hold, by:

• Calling this telephone number (952-469-3454 or 1-877-394-4930)   
• Letter sent to:  
 Learner’s Edge Office Manager   
10523 165th St. W.  
Lakeville, MN 55044

Upon request (per the noted methods above), we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data that we keep about you, within a month (proof of your identity may be required). We will provide the information without any charge.  
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data:

• erased   
• rectified or amended   
• completed

We reserve the right to refuse to provide a copy of your personal data, but will give reasons for our refusal.We do, however, allow you to challenge our decision to refuse to provide you with a copy of your personal data.

Upon your request and to the extent your request does not compromise our privacy or security policies; we will update and correct personal information you have provided to us. In addition, we will honor all requests to remove your name from our solicitation efforts by modifying our database to ensure that no further contact is made with you. Please allow 6-8 weeks for the changes to take effect due to the lead times required for mailing preparation. If you wish to update your information, you may do so by sending us an e-mail that identifies the information you with to have updated. If you wish to remove your name from our solicitation efforts, simply send us an email at [info@LearnersEdgeInc.com](mailto:info@LearnersEdgeInc.com) or call at (952) 469-3454 or toll free: 1-877-394-4930.

**Internet Protocol Address:**   
We collect an IP address from all visitors to our Site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server,administer our Site, analyze trends, track users' movement, gather broad demographic information for aggregate use in order for us to improve the site, and deliver customized, personalized content. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Use of "Cookies":**   
Our Site may use cookies to enhance your experience while using our Site. Cookies are pieces of information that some Web sites transfer to the computer that is browsing that Web site and are used for record-keeping purposes at many Web sites. Use of cookies makes Web-surfing easier by performing certain functions such as saving your passwords, your personal preferences regarding your use of the particular Web site and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. Many consider the use of cookies to be an industry standard.

Your browser is probably set to accept cookies. However, if you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to have your browser refuse cookies, it is possible that some areas of our Site will not function properly when you view them.

**Security:**   
All information provided to Learner’s Edge is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. We also protect account information by placing it on a secure portion of our Site that is only accessible by certain qualified employees of Learner’s Edge. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. While we strive to protect your information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of such information.

**Other Web Sites:**   
Our Site contains links to other Web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another Web site for which Learner’s Edge has no responsibility. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on all such sites as their policies may be different than ours.

**Contacting Us:**   
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact:

Learner’s Edge  
10523 165th St. W.  
Lakeville, MN 55044

You can also send an email to: [info@LearnersEdgeInc.com](mailto:info@LearnersEdgeInc.com)
